Inventory of the Raymond Benjamin West papers, 1901-1918
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
Raymond Benjamin West papers
1901-1918
West, Raymond Benjamin, 1875-
00031
5.85 cubic feet (13 boxes)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
Biography of Raymond Benjamin West
Raymond Benjamin West (1875- ) was a lawyer in Basin, Wyoming.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of correspondence regarding court cases (1901-1918) and West's extensive legal files of court cases dealing with water rights, mining and petroleum companies and the collection of debts (1904-1918).
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions on the materials for research purposes, and the collection is open to the public.
Related Materials
There are no known other archival collections created by Raymond Benjamin West at the date of processing.
Acquisition Information
The collection was received from Mrs. W.A. Towne in 1946.
Access Terms
Mines and mineral resources -- West (U.S.); Petroleum industry and trade -- West (U.S.); Practice of law -- Wyoming -- Basin.; Water rights -- West (U.S.); Debt -- West (U.S.); Basin (Wyo.) -- History.; Wyoming -- History -- 1890-1918.; Legal files.; Lawyers.
Mines and Mineral Resources; Water and Water Rights; Laws and Legislation; Civil Procedure and Courts; Politics, Government, and Law; Wyoming
Container List
- General Material:
  - Bills (Box 1)
  - Checks & Receipts (Box 1)
  - Correspondence:
    - undated (Box 1)
    - 1901 - 1903 (Box 1)
    - 1904 (Box 1)
    - 1905 - 1917 (Box 1)
    - 1918 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Notes and Items (Box 1)
  - Pamphlets:
    - Nebraska Gamma Theta (Box 1)
    - Speech of Hon. Jonathan Bourne, Jr., 1911 (Box 1)
    - Wisconsin Primary Law, 1907 (Box 1)
  - Unidentified Photographs (one filed in photo file B-M613jg), 1907 (Box 1)
- Legal Case File Folders:
  - A's Miscellaneous (Box 2)
  - Abplanalp, S. P. (Box 2)
  - Adams - Fellansbee, etc. (Box 2)
  - Adams & Matson (Box 2)
  - Alden, Geo D. (Box 2)
  - Alexander, Myra E. (Box 2)
  - Allen, John - Nicholson Land (Box 2)
  - Alley, Moustafa (Box 2)
  - Allison, J. P. (Box 2)
  - Alpha Tua Omega Frat. (Box 2)
  - Altman, B. & Co. (Box 2)
  - The American Credit Co. (Box 2)
  - American Law Book Co. (Box 2)
  - American Steel Wire Co. (Box 2)
  - American Surety Co. (Box 2)
  - Anderson, Lee Glass (Box 2)
  - Andre, Wm. H. (Box 2)
  - Anheuser Bush Co. (Box 2)
  - Arbens, Geo vs. Reffner, C. F. (Box 2)
  - Armstrong, J. E. vs. Franklin G. Tolman (Box 2)
  - Arnoldus, Mrs. Bell (Box 2)
  - Atherly, Clyde U. (Box 2)
  - Attorney General (Box 2)
  - Auto Accessory and Speedometer Co. (Box 2)
  - Axtell, Clifford W. (Box 2)
  - B's Misc. (Box 2)
  - Babcock, Frank (Box 2)
  - Babcock, L. L. (Box 2)
  - Babson Bros. (Box 2)
  - Bader, Fred L. (Box 2)
  - Baird, John L. (Box 2)
  - Baldridge, Keller & Keller (Box 2)
  - Bancroft Whitney & Co. (Box 2)
  - Bankers Life Ins. Co. (Box 2)
  - Barnee, H. K. (Box 2)
  - Barrett, Jesse W. (Box 2)
  - Barry & Wellington (Box 2)
  - Barrows, F. H. (Box 2)
  - Barrows, Grace W. (Box 2)
  - Basin State Bk. (Box 2)
  - Bassett, Dave (Box 2)
  - Beaton, Angus (Box 2)
  - Bee Publishing Co. (Box 2)
  - Benbrooks, W. T. (Box 2)
  - Bennett, W. S. (Box 2)
  - Berringer, A. M. vs Halletal (Box 2)
  - Berringer, A. M. vs Republic Oil Co. (Box 2)
  - Berry, J. A. (Box 2)
  - Berry, J. A., 1908-1910 (Box 3)
  - Berry Brothers, 1911-1917 (Box 3)
  - Bethold, Joseph F. (Box 3)
  - Big Fork Ditch Co. vs. W. Lindsay (Box 3)
  - Big Horn Basin Republican League (Box 3)
  - Big Horn Cty Irrigating Co. (Box 3)
  - Billings Hdw. Co. (Box 3)
  - Billings Milling Co. (Box 3)
  - Billings Sugar Co. (Box 3)
  - Binford & Farber (Box 3)
  - Block, Edward (Box 3)
  - Bloom, D. F. (Box 3)
  - Bosch, M. (Box 3)
  - Bowman, E. P. (Box 3)
  - Bowman, L. A. (Box 3)
  - Boyd Pump Co. (Box 3)
  - Boyle, Albert C. (Box 3)
  - Brockett, R. & Co. (Box 3)
  - Bradenburg, W. H. (Box 3)
  - Brown, E. E. vs. Paul Freeman (Box 3)
  - Carey, Joseph M. (Box 3)
  - Commissioner of Public Lands (Box 3)
  - Cray Accts (Box 3)
  - Credit Clearing House (Box 3)
  - Cromer, Bryant S. (Box 3)
  - Crystoll Creek Oil Land (Box 3)
  - Crown Cigar Co. vs. J. S. Erickson (Box 3)
  - Culbertson, Roger (Box 3)
  - Cusack, Ed (Box 3)
  - D's Miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - Dailey School (Box 4)
  - Daniels, Chas. (Box 4)
  - Daniels & Fisher Stores Co. (Box 4)
  - Dana & Blount (Box 4)
  - Darrah, H. N. (Box 4)
  - Davis, Elsie (Box 4)
  - Davis, Irvan (Box 4)
  - Davis, Irvan (Mrs.) (Box 4)
  - Deegan, Margaret (Box 4)
  - Denny vs. Berry (Box 4)
  - Devon Mfg. Co. (Box 4)
  - Dobson, Alice (Box 4)
  - Dodge & Webber (Box 4)
  - Domberger, T. (Box 4)
  - Donaldson Fruit Co. vs. Ewers (Box 4)
  - Downs, J. J. (Box 4)
  - Dowsen, B. E. (Box 4)
  - Drake, Dell vs. State of Wyo. (Box 4)
  - Draydon, W. H. (Box 4)
  - Duboise, Wm. (Box 4)
  - Dudley & Patterson vs. Reynolds & Sypher (Box 4)
  - Duluth Show Case Co. vs. Deaver Merc. Co. (Box 4)
  - Durfy - Severson (Box 4)
  - Durham, Royal E. (Box 4)
  - Eastern M & C Ass'n (Box 4)
  - Economy Advertising Co. (Box 4)
  - Edick, Mrs. Margaret S. (Box 4)
  - Edmunds, H. D. (Box 4)
  - Edwards, W. B. vs. Porter, C. B. (Box 4)
  - Egnew, R. C. (Box 4)
  - Election - 1914 Judge of Dist. Courts - Wyoming (Box 4)
  - Eliason, R. (Box 4)
  - Ellington, E. (Box 4)
  - Empire Ring Co. vs. Ruby Sheltz (Box 4)
  - Enders vs. Thompson (Box 4)
  - Enterline, E. E. (Box 4)
  - Enterline & Lee Fleiche (Box 4)
  - Erickson, A. W. (Box 4)
  - Ewart, L. R. (Box 4)
  - Fagin, Thos. J. & Co. (Box 4)
  - Fanning, C. C. (Box 5)
  - Farnier, Roy (Box 5)
  - Farmers State Bank (Box 5)
  - Farwell, Ozmun, Kirk & Co. (Box 5)
  - Farwell, Osmund, Kirk & Co. (Box 5)
  - Federal School vs. J. R. Engle (Box 5)
  - Ferdinand Westheimer & Sons (Box 5)
  - Fitfield, Fay vs. R. B. West (Box 5)
  - First National Bank (Box 5)
  - First National Bank - Buffalo (Box 5)
  - First National Bank - Meeteetse (Box 5)
  - First National Bank - Worland (Box 5)
  - First National Bank - Worland, et al (Box 5)
  - Flittner, Arthur (Box 5)
  - Flockhart, Jack (Box 5)
  - Forrest, F. J. (Box 5)
  - Frantz, L. L. (Box 5)
  - Freeman, Jos. W. (Box 5)
  - Fritz Ditch Co. vs. C. B. & A. R. R. (Box 5)
  - Funk, Carl (Box 5)
  - G's Miscellaneous (Box 5)
  - Gallup, J. D. (Box 5)
  - Gamble Robinson Co. vs. Consumer Supply Co. (Box 5)
  - Gantt, E. D. (Box 5)
  - Gapen, Frank (Box 5)
  - Gazette Printing Co. (Box 5)
  - Gardner, Clarence (Box 5)
  - Gardner, Dr. J. W. (Box 5)
  - Garnett & Garnett (Box 5)
  - Garrison, John C. (Box 5)
  - Gates, H. B. (Box 5)
  - Gebhart, Mrs. (Box 5)
  - George, Dr. P. S. (Box 5)
  - German Seed House (Box 5)
  - Gifford, Henry (Box 5)
  - Glacier Fish Co. vs. J. Mansfield (Box 5)
  - Glenn, Ira (Box 5)
  - Glover & Co. vs. Pease Peterson (Box 5)
  - Goddard & Clark (Box 5)
  - Goodrick, Mrs. Hazel (Box 5)
  - Goodyear vs. Pease-Peterson Co. (Box 5)
  - Gould, R. A. (Box 5)
  - Grabbart, Frank (Box 5)
  - Grain Belt Milling Co. vs. Lotman (Box 5)
  - Graves, Geo. W. (Box 5)
  - Graves, J. W. (Box 5)
  - Gray, W. O. (Box 5)
  - Greunig, J. G. (Box 5)
  - Greybull Standard (Box 5)
  - Griffin, J. B. (Box 5)
  - Griswold, Edward H. (Box 5)
  - The Grolier Society (Box 5)
  - Grould, L. E. (Box 5)
  - Groves, J. H. (Box 5)
  - Gruenig, G. C. (Box 5)
  - Guinn, C. C. (Box 5)
  - Guyor, H. W. (Box 5)
  - H's Miscellaneous (Box 5)
  - Hageman, A. B. (Box 6)
  - Hake Brome Hake (Worland) (Box 6)
  - Hale, R. W. Dr. (Box 6)
  - Hall, Clyde C. (Box 6)
  - Hallum, Louis (Box 6)
  - Hammond, Fred F. (Box 6)
  - Harding & Hamilton (Box 6)
  - Harkins, C. H. (Box 6)
  - Harrington, D. (Box 6)
  - Harris, H. E. (Box 6)
  - Harris & Harris vs. D. C. Hewey (Box 6)
  - Harris Mechanic (Box 6)
  - Harrison Accts (Box 6)
  - Hart, Boies C. (Box 6)
  - Hart Investment Co. (Box 6)
  - Hart Ins. Co. vs. L. J. Willis (Box 6)
  - Hartigan, Ga. (Box 6)
  - Hasemerer, Mrs. E. (Box 6)
  - Hastings Industrial Co. (Box 6)
  - Hays, W. D. (Box 6)
  - Healy, Walter E. (Box 6)
  - Heiden, Christian (Box 6)
  - Helman, Moulton Whitman & Whitman (Box 6)
  - Hennessy, John T. (Box 6)
  - Henry, Joe (Box 6)
  - Henshaw vs. Pure Oil Co. (Box 6)
  - Hensley, F. C. (Burlington State Bank) (Box 6)
  - Herold, Chapin Ins. (Box 6)
  - Herold Tailoring Co. vs. Martendale (Box 6)
  - Hill, T. B. (Box 6)
  - Hillsbergy, Henry (Box 6)
  - Hirsch, S. Distilling Co. (Box 6)
  - Hobart, Charles E. (Box 6)
  - Hobart vs. Ewers (Box 6)
  - Hohn vs. Hohn (Box 6)
  - Holmes, Gus (Box 6)
  - Hopkins, S. G. (Box 6)
  - Hovey, Frederick (Box 6)
  - International Book Co. (Box 6)
  - International Conservatory of Music, Dallas, TX (Box 7)
  - International Harvester Co. (Box 7)
  - Jackson (Box 7)
  - Jessen, Alice (Box 7)
  - Jewell Nursery Co. vs. Dr. F. M. Booth (Box 7)
  - Johnson vs. Johnson (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Ephraim (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Ira (Box 7)
  - Jones, Elmer J. Est (Box 7)
  - Jones, F. I. (Box 7)
  - Joslin, B. J. vs. First National Bank (Box 7)
  - Kabo Corset vs. McKinzie, C. F. (Box 7)
  - Kaufman vs. Sheldon (Box 7)
  - Kebler, Mrs. H. E. (Box 7)
  - Keefe - Davidson Co. (Box 7)
  - Keeley, Carl M. (Box 7)
  - Kepford, W. A. (Box 7)
  - Kelley, T. S. (Box 7)
  - Kennedy, T. Blake (Box 7)
  - Kennedy Estate (Box 7)
  - Kimball Aff. (Box 7)
  - Kinaman, Mary (Box 7)
  - Kenney, J. F. (Box 7)
  - Knapp & Spencer Co. (Box 7)
  - Knisely, A. J. (Box 7)
  - Krung Brewing Co. (Box 7)
  - Kurrock, Lila B. (Box 7)
  - Kutchler, Calvin (Box 7)
  - L's Miscellaneous (Box 7)
  - Lacey & Lacey (Box 8)
  - Laford, Gus (Box 8)
  - Land, Collins, Campbell, Wood & Leavitt (Box 8)
  - Land Office (Box 8)
  - LaSalle Extension cs. Tucker, C. H. (Box 8)
  - Laub, Chas. (Box 8)
  - Lawson, J. H. (Box 8)
  - Lawyers Co-operative Merc. Agency (Box 8)
  - Lawyers Co-operative Pub. Co. (Box 8)
  - Leavitt vs. John Dallen (Box 8)
  - Lee, Ray E. Com. Public Lands (Box 8)
  - Lee Automatic Co. (Box 8)
  - Leslie's vs. O'Niel Rf. Extra (Box 8)
  - Lewis, J. E. (Box 8)
  - Library (Box 8)
  - Lincoln Potter Co. vs. D. V. Early (Box 8)
  - Lincoln State Journal (Box 8)
  - Lindsay & Co. (Box 8)
  - Little, Frank A. (Box 8)
  - Lonabaugh, E. E. (Box 8)
  - Loring, Charles (Box 8)
  - Losekamp, J. P. (Box 8)
  - Lovell (Town of) (Box 8)
  - Lyons, Henry (Box 8)
  - McAdams, T. M. (Box 8)
  - McClellan, O. N. (Box 9)
  - McCray, Eva A. (Box 9)
  - McDonald, Chas. (Box 9)
  - McDonald vs. Benge (Box 9)
  - McDonald Co. vs. Baxter (Box 9)
  - McDonald Chocolate Co. vs. Big Horn Drug Co. (Box 9)
  - McFarland, Robert R. (Box 9)
  - McGilton Gains & Smith (Box 9)
  - McGintie & Andrews (Box 9)
  - McGuffy, A. J. (Box 9)
  - McKenney, J. F. (Box 9)
  - McLaughlin, James (Box 9)
  - McLaughlin, Katherine (Box 9)
  - McNally, Wm. (Box 9)
  - Madeen and Madeen (Box 9)
  - Malarhey, Searbrook & Dibble (Box 9)
  - Mann, Chas. B. (Box 9)
  - Manning, Ed. (Box 9)
  - Mapes, B. L. (Box 9)
  - Marchout, Gib (Box 9)
  - Marshall, Davis & Asher (Box 9)
  - Marshall Field & Co. (Box 9)
  - Marshall Jackson & Co. (Box 9)
  - Marten, Willa (Box 9)
  - Marten, Fraser & Speir (Box 9)
  - Martendale Legal Directory (Box 9)
  - Mason, S. W. Foreclosure (Box 9)
  - Masonic Matters (Box 9)
  - Matson, R. N. (Box 9)
  - May, J. P. (Box 9)
  - Mayor, H. B. (Box 9)
  - Mead, Henry (Box 9)
  - Meeteetse Merc. Co. (Box 9)
  - Merchant's Protective Ass'n (Box 9)
  - Metcalf, E. D. (Box 9)
  - Metcalf, Orlando (Box 9)
  - Metz - Sackett (Box 9)
  - Militia - Wyoming National Guard (Box 9)
  - Miller, Bellie (Box 9)
  - Minus, G. F. vs. Dr. F. A. Minus (Box 9)
  - Mishawaka Woolen Co. vs. Snyder, F. A. (Box 9)
  - Mochon, A. (Box 9)
  - Moncure, Cockrell (Box 9)
  - Mondell, Frank W. (Box 9)
  - Monroe, L. G. Sec. Billings Com. Club (Box 9)
  - Montana Nursery Co. (Box 9)
  - Montgomery Hall & Young (Box 9)
  - Mordie, P. M. (Box 9)
  - Morris, D. L. M. (Box 9)
  - Morris, McLaughlin Murphy vs. Erickson, J. A. (Box 9)
  - Morrison, E. R. (Box 9)
  - Morse, A. H. (Box 9)
  - Mudd, Fred (Box 9)
  - Mullen, W. E. (Box 9)
  - Munter & Flood (Box 9)
  - Mutual Live Stock Co. vs. Kelly, J. S. (Box 9)
  - Nagel, Fred C. (Box 9)
  - National Geographical Society (Box 10)
  - National Life Ins. Co. (Box 10)
  - National Merc. Adjust Bureau (Box 10)
  - Neely, Mrs. R. S. (Box 10)
  - Neiber, Mary N. (Box 10)
  - Noe, R. P. (Box 10)
  - Northern Bridge, Co. (Box 10)
  - Odom, A. H. (Box 10)
  - Oeland, W. S. (Box 10)
  - Oliver Typewriter Co. vs. F. J. Sylvester (Box 10)
  - Olson, Albert (Box 10)
  - Oil Land Leasing Bill (Box 10)
  - Omaha Baum Iron Store vs. Motos Sales and Service Co. (Box 10)
  - Omaha Printing Co. (Box 10)
  - Owl Creek Coal Co. (Box 10)
  - The Pacific National Bank (Box 10)
  - Pattee, E. D. (Box 10)
  - Paxton & Gallagher vs. F. A. Snyder & Co. (Box 10)
  - Pelz, Leon S. (Box 10)
  - Peterson, William (Box 10)
  - Pioneer Adjustment Co. (Box 10)
  - Pioneer Trust & Savings Bank (Box 10)
  - Pitts, Wm. L. (Box 10)
  - Pittsbury Commercial Exchange (Box 10)
  - Politics - Wyoming (Box 10)
  - Preston, D. A., 1910 - 1912 (Box 10)
  - Ptah, F. (Box 10)
  - Pure Oil Co. vs. Flanders (Box 10)
  - Quiner, Mr. (Box 10)
  - Rach Island Plow Co. (Box 10)
  - Ranch & Messer (Box 11)
  - Randolph, Geo & L. P. Thompson (Box 11)
  - Ray, Dell M. (Box 11)
  - Receipted Bills (Box 11)
  - Reesy, James U. (Box 11)
  - Registry Cards and Receipts (Box 11)
  - Rellinghouse Notes (Box 11)
  - Remington Typewriter Co. (Box 11)
  - Reser, W. O. Dr. (Box 11)
  - Reynolds, D. W. (Box 11)
  - Ridgely, H. S. (Box 11)
  - Robertson, B. Y. (Box 11)
  - Rockas, William (Box 11)
  - Rollin, H. Ayers (Box 11)
  - Ross, Dr. H. E. vs. Chas. W. Anderson (Box 11)
  - Ross, Robet (Box 11)
  - Rumsey, B. C. (Box 11)
  - Russell, J. S. & Co. (Box 11)
  - Saban, J. P. (Box 11)
  - Sanders, Christian Co. (Box 11)
  - Sarver, C. A. (Box 11)
  - Scambler, Geo (Box 11)
  - Scientific American (Box 11)
  - Scott, P. (Box 11)
  - Seaman, John (Box 11)
  - Searls, J. W. & Co. (Box 11)
  - Seaton, Rod (Box 11)
  - Security Merc. Co. (Box 11)
  - Sellers, T. L. (Box 11)
  - Shafer, W. L. (Box 11)
  - Shafer Mining Claims (Box 11)
  - Shedd Sizer Co. (Box 11)
  - Shell Creek Cattleman's Ass'n (Box 11)
  - Shell Telephone Co. (Box 11)
  - Shenkberg, G. Co. (Box 11)
  - Shepherd, Earnest (Box 11)
  - Shepherd, Lizzie E. (Box 11)
  - Shoemaker, W. C. (Box 11)
  - Simmons, John S. (Box 11)
  - Simon Binswanger & Bro. (Box 11)
  - Simpson & Donley (Box 11)
  - Skaulding, S. J. (Box 11)
  - Slabaugh, W. W. (Box 11)
  - Smith, Dr. M. H. (Box 11)
  - Smith, W. R. (Box 11)
  - Snow, William C. (Box 11)
  - Sommers, G. vs. D. V. Early (Box 11)
  - Sioux Falls Point & Glass Co. vs. A. V. Olson (Box 11)
  - Spanish War Veterans in Nebr. (Box 11)
  - Stafford, C. M. (Box 11)
  - Stanton, B. (Box 11)
  - Stine vs. Renner (Box 11)
  - Stid, C. W. (Box 11)
  - Stock Growers Bank (Box 11)
  - Stone & Winslow (Box 11)
  - Stowe, Ed. E. (Box 11)
  - Straus & Schram, Inc. vs. Halon, J. B. (Box 11)
  - Street, Chas. M. (Box 11)
  - Striker, L. V. (Box 11)
  - Supreme Court Clerk (Box 11)
  - Swank, W. R. (Box 11)
  - Swenson, J. A. (Box 11)
  - Swenson, Oscar (Box 11)
  - Sykes, Edmund vs. James H. Montgomery (Box 11)
  - Teeters, J. L. & Co. (Box 11)
  - Terrell, C. A. (Box 12)
  - Tescher, et al vs. Reynolds & Sypher (Box 12)
  - Thayer, Mrs. Wm. (Box 12)
  - Therer, Clarke Walter & Mernham (Box 12)
  - Therer, Clarke Walter vs. O. L. Gilbet (Box 12)
  - Thomas, Atwood C. (Box 12)
  - Thomas, Mrs. F. E. (Box 12)
  - Thompson, B. F. (Box 12)
  - Thompson, L. C. (Box 12)
  - Tillard, Daisy A. (Box 12)
  - Tilley, J. H. (Box 12)
  - Todd Proctograph Co. vs. R. J. Extra (Box 12)
  - Turner, K. M. (Box 12)
  - Union School Furnishing Co. (Box 12)
  - Unique Ills. Co. vs. H. C. Whitmore (Box 12)
  - United Merc. Agency (Box 12)
  - U. S. Fidelity & Guaranty Co. (Box 12)
  - U. S. Land Office - Buffalo (Box 12)
  - U. S. Rubber Co. vs. Chas. McDonald (Box 12)
  - U. S. Supply Co. vs. Claff (Box 12)
  - Utah & Wyoming Oil Co. (Box 12)
  - Vanchees, Wm. (Box 12)
  - VanHorn, J. H. (Box 12)
  - Vaterlaus, C. S. (Box 12)
  - Vaterlaus, Emil (Box 12)
  - Vernon Law Book Co. (Box 12)
  - Vincent, F. B. (Box 12)
  - W's Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - Wahn, Clarence A. (Box 12)
  - Waldo & Cunningham (Box 12)
  - Walker, H. B. (Box 12)
  - Walls, W. L. (Box 12)
  - Waln, Claude vs. Sam Skovill (Box 12)
  - Walsh, Nolan (Box 12)
  - Walters, Chas. E. &Co. (Box 12)
  - Ward, Nelson (Box 12)
  - Ward, R. D. (Box 12)
  - Warner, Clyde (Box 12)
  - Warner, Morris (Box 12)
  - Warner, Steve (Box 12)
  - Watt, A. H. (Box 12)
  - Watters, T. E. (Box 12)
  - Watts, Clyde M. (Box 12)
  - Webster, Constance (Box 12)
  - Welley vs. Welley (Box 12)
  - Wells, P. A. (Box 12)
  - Wells Co. (Box 12)
  - Weazell, D. C. (Box 12)
  - West, C. C. (Box 12)
  - West, D. C. (Box 12)
  - West, Mary (Box 12)
  - West, R. B. (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - West Publishing Co. (Box 13)
  - Westhermier, Ferdinand (Box 13)
  - Weston, H. R. (Box 13)
  - Whaley, J. B. (Box 13)
  - Whaley vs. Mosegard (Box 13)
  - Whipple, Walter (Box 13)
  - Whitaker & Co. (Box 13)
  - White, Frank (Box 13)
  - White Sewing Machine Co. vs. Schlof, A. E. (Box 13)
  - Whitney, A. P. (Box 13)
  - Whittemore, Eula I. (Box 13)
  - Wilbur Merc. Agcy (Box 13)
  - Wilbur Merc. Co. (Box 13)
  - Wiles, T. F. (Box 13)
  - Wilkerson, C. M. (Box 13)
  - Williams, C. J. Mayor of Greybull (Box 13)
  - Williams, Clarence (Box 13)
  - Williams, Geo F. (Box 13)
  - Williams, Hunter & Guffin (Box 13)
  - Williams Shoe Co. vs. J. S. Erickson (Box 13)
  - Williams, Louis vs. Equity Oil Co. (Box 13)
  - Wilson, C. S. (Box 13)
  - Wilson, Esta (Box 13)
  - Wilson, John *Humane Office (Box 13)
  - Wilson, W. (Box 13)
  - Winslow, Dan (Box 13)
  - Winslow, L. E. (Box 13)
  - Winslow, Stone (Box 13)
  - Winters, C. E. (Box 13)
  - Wingenried, Albet C. (Box 13)
  - Wise, F. A. (Box 13)
  - Wyman, W. H. (Box 13)
  - Wyman Patridge Co. vs. Thermopolis Merc. Co. (Box 13)
  - Wyoming Land & Irrigation (Box 13)
  - Y's Miscellaneous (Box 13)
  - Young, James (Box 13)
  - Ziegler, Issdor (Box 13)